retaggr.com 2011-05-30

# Retaggr - The Definitive Online Profile

Retaggr.com collects your email address as part of the retaggr service. We will never rent or sell your email address. We hate spam as much as you do.

**Your Profile Card**

The retaggr system allows you to create a “Profile Card”.  This information will always include your full name, and may also contain any personal information that you have entered into retaggr, including (but not limited to) information from third party systems that you have allowed retaggr to access, images of you, your biography, contact details, and other personal information.

This information will be available, and potentially displayed on all retaggr enabled websites, or anywhere where your Profile Card is embedded.

**Information Collection and Use**

retaggr will not use the personal information you or other sites have provided, for purposes other than display on the retaggr site and other retaggr enabled sites.

·        If you have chosen to opt-in to email notifications, you may periodically receive emails from retaggr.

·        Others may enter your email address to invite you to join the retaggr community. retaggr may use your email address to invite you to join retaggr.

·        Others may use a third party communication system to identify you.  retaggr may use said system to invite you to join retaggr.

·        Others may “tag” you in images.  Retaggr may use your email address, and/or other third party communication systems, to inform you about these tags.

If you wish to change the way information in your retaggr card is displayed, you may log in to your retaggr account and adjust your communication preferences. 

You may completely remove your retaggr card from all retaggr enabled sites by terminating your account.

**Retrieving information from third party accounts**

If you choose to allow retaggr to interact with third party systems you will be requested to provide login information for this third party account. Your password will not be stored on the retaggr servers and will only be used for the request. 

Any details retrieved will only be used to automate your use of retaggr and will never be shared, sold or rented.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

retaggr may update this privacy policy at any time and for any reason. If there are major changes to how we handle your personal information, we will send notification to the primary registered email address against your account, or by placing an easily accessible notice on our site of such changes. If you do not agree to abide by any changes made in the privacy policy, you may remedy the situation by deleting your account and ceasing to use retaggr in the future. 

We take your privacy seriously and you are always in control to decide which of your details should be visible on your public retaggr card. If you have any questions regarding our policy, email us at [privacy@retaggr.com](mailto:privacy@retaggr.com).
